<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lake Merritt Guide</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="place_name">Place name</string>
    <string name="listAddress">place location</string>
    <string name="search_hint">search</string>
    <string name="address_info">address here</string>

    <string name="portal_info">Portal, the best restaurant and open-air beer garden in Oakland, is a beer garden with a large out-door patio with breath-taking view of the Lake Merritt. Order some delicious food made from only the best fresh ingredients and pair it with one of our top notch gourmet beers. </string>
    <string name="grandLakeKitchen_info">Grand Lake Kitchen is a great breakfast place. The service here is outstanding, friendly and efficient. Grand Lake Kitchen\’s have a great patio out front with umbrellas and a view of the Lake.</string>
    <string name="jongGA_info">Jong Ga serve from traditional Hanjeongsik to All You Can Eat BBQ with a varied array of Banchans \(side dishes\). Since 2000, We are an authentic Korean restaurant committed to serving the finest traditional Korean cuisine. Jong Ga House, meaning the eldest son\'s house or the head family. We have been serving the bay area since 2000 and have been garnering favorable reviews. We serve Korean barbeques and hanjeongsik, a full-course Korean meal with a varied array of banchan. Our head chef is an expert in the Korean royal court cuisine and has been preparing authentic Korean meals for more than 30 years. Our commitment to quality and friendly service will make your dining experience very pleasurable, and we will continue to uphold a high standard of quality in serving fine Korean cuisine. When you enter our restaurant, you will be notice with our beautiful Hanok interior. Hanok is a term to describe Korean traditional houses and it has long been built on the soil of the Korean peninsula. A Hanok has a framework involving a stylobate (a stepped platform as the foundation of the structure) at the bottom,and the placement of wooden pillars, beams, rafters and titles at the top. The raw materials used in Hanok, such as soil, timber, and rock, are all natural and recyclable and do not cause pollution. This unique traditional house that has been formed through a long period of time possesses practicality and artistic beauty, and we hope that those who visit our restaurant can see the merits of the Korean traditional house.</string>
    <string name="rockinCrawfish_info">\nWhether you are a transplant to California from New Orleans, the Crawfish capital of the world, or you just crave the sheer unbridled joy of great seafood eating, you will always remember the day that you found one of our Rockin\' Crawfish locations in Oakland or Concord or San Pablo in Northern California. \nOur delicious seafood has a uniquely Cajun flavor that we know you will love. We also offer a full line of beverages including both Domestic and Imported Beers, Sake, or delicious Sakitinis served with your choice of fruit from lychees to mango or peach. \nFor starters we offer an appetizer list that is sure to have something you\'re craving. Choose from Cajun chili cheese fries or Buffalo wings to seafood gumbo or oysters on the half shell, but remember to†save room for your main course! On our menu you will find great Cajun seafood offerings including crawfish, crab, shrimp, clams and oysters, and for families we\'ve included some kid friendly items as well, like chicken strips with fries. Add your choice of sides, including rice, potatoes or corn, and your dinner is complete. And don\'t think we\'ve forgotten about desert - you will love our fried Oreos with strawberries and ice cream. \nYou only enter Rockin\' Crawfish once as a stranger - by the time you leave you will love our food and come back often.</string>
    <string name="haddonHill_info">A Nice cozy atmosphere for drinks. It\'s tiny, yet adorable neighborhood cafe serving quality coffee drinks and solid snacks. The owner and staff here are incredibly warm and inviting.</string>
    <string name="arizmendiBakery_info">At Arizmendi Bakery on Lakeshore, we offer our community artisan breads, morning pastries and gourmet pizza, prepared right in front of you and brought fresh from our ovens daily. Our focus is on providing healthy food using straightforward recipes and quality ingredients. Ask us for a list of our organic ingredients. Our ovens are running all day long. Stop by early for hot muffins, scones and pastries, including some vegan treats. For lunch or dinner, we offer a unique vegetarian pizza of the day featuring seasonal vegetables, infused oils, and fresh herbs on organic, thin sourdough crust. And our signature sourdoughs and hearty wheat breads are hot out of the oven mornings and afternoons. You\’ll also find a rotating selection of fresh green salads and spreads in our deli case, as well as soups made from scratch. Arizmendi is the shortened name of Jose Maria Arizmendiarrieta, a young priest who inspired and helped found the Mondragon Cooperatives in the Basque Country of Spain in the 1950s. Although worker cooperatives have functioned in most parts of the world since the 19th century, the success of the Mondragon Cooperatives has attracted worldwide attention. What started as one firm and roughly 25 people in 1956 is now a major international business with a work force of over 100,000, employed in some 250+ worker-owned enterprises and affiliated organizations.</string>
    <string name="michelBistro_info">We are proud to introduce Michel Bistro ñ a new concept of French bistro. We are from Provence in the south of France and are excited to share our love of cuisine and all that it entails with Oakland. Our goal is to bring to Lakeshore avenue a bistro that offers French dishes with a modern twist, made with high quality products in a relaxed setting. Our signature drink is Pastis, a famous aperitif from Marseille. We want our guests to experience our warm Southern French culture that brings people together with good food, drinks, and atmosphere. We are excited to become part of the community and look forward to creating long-lasting relationships with our customers.</string>
    <string name="theAlley_info">The Alley is voted one of Oakland\’s greatest dive bars. You do not have to be a drinker to enjoy this bar either, as they have a great greasy spoon type menu. The atmosphere is inviting, and the ambience is dark. There are a million business cards on the walls (probably holding them together) and they also line the tables. Some of the cards look like they have been there as long as the building. There is live karaoke on Sunday nights and this was the thing that everyone can experienced.</string>
    <string name="offTheGrid_info">Off the Grid began in June 2010 with the simple idea that grouping Street Food vendors together would create an experience that would allow neighbors to connect with friends, and families to reconnect with each other. Since then Off the Grid has worked hard to develop markets that are both located in urban cores of cities, and that utilize spaces that are not easily activated effectively throughout the day. \nOff the Grid has become a Bay Area icon and quintessential San Franciscan activity, providing unique food and cultural experiences connecting friends, families, and communities in a shared space. We seek to maintain a shared sense of space by collaborating with local businesses and communities to activate novel public spaces with truly unique experiences. We currently operate 45+ weekly public markets throughout the San Francisco Bay Area. One of the signature aspects of Off the Grid is the diverse group of 200+ food, bar, and amenity vendors that we work with on a weekly basis, ensuring a diversity of cuisine options. We use these vendors in Off the Grid catering, offering full production catering for groups ranging from 100-10,000. At our core, we believe in the power of a shared food experience to connect communities, and we work hard to maintain a shared sense of space wherever we serve.</string>
    <string name="theGardenInfo">Admission is free for the seven acres of groomed gardens. Some of the most popular areas include the bonsai garden, which has special hours, and the sensory garden, which includes lavender, lime, chives, and other scented plants. A wooded, Japanese-style area at the center of the garden can be entered by crossing under atorii, a traditional Japanese gate gifted to Oakland by the city of Fukuoka, Japan. The gardens are a great spot to take lunch or a book, or to just go on a quiet walk. The Friends of the Gardens at Lake Merritt oversees garden development and welcomes volunteers.</string>
    <string name="japaneseGardenInfo"> Hisaichi Harry Tsugawa designed our Japanese garden. It was built in 1959 by members of the Japanese American community of Oakland and the East Bay, supported by the California Association of Nurserymen, Oakland chapter of the Japanese American Citizens League, and various citizens and businesses. \nBy the mid 1980\'s the garden had suffered from lack of maintenance and then Vice Mayor Frank Ogawa asked Dennis Makishima to bring his students to the garden to improve it. Makishima had initiated the Aesthetic Pruning classes at Merritt College. \nThe Aesthetic Pruning Club started maintaining this garden in 1985. Now under the direction of Bill Castellon, it continues to provide maintenance and improvements. The Friends of the Japanese Garden was formed to raise funds so that the Merritt College landscape irrigation class could install the irrigation system. \nThe traditional Japanese gate, and the fence which surrounds the garden, were funded by the Creative Work Fund, with the Lake Merritt Breakfast Club and other philanthropic organizations, and built and installed by Jay van Arsdale, the hand-tool carpentry instructor at Laney College, and his students. The Merritt College Aesthetic Pruning Club provides monthly maintenance and twice yearly daylong pruning workshops for the garden.</string>
    <string name="palmGardenInfo"> Palm Garden, the Palmetum, is at the back of the Gardens at Lake Merritt. It\’s considered the most extensive established collection of cool Mediterranean and high altitude tropical palms in the United States! The Palmetum features a great variety of palm species native to cool and warm Mediterranean climates and tropical high altitude regions of Europe, Asia, Australia, Africa and the Americas. Oakland\’s unique sub-tropical micro-climate provides the perfect growing conditions to nurture this collection.</string>
    <string name="mediterraneanGardenInfo">The site is unique and beautiful. The Palmetum is a dramatic backdrop with its large palms and colorful tropical plants. The historic Easterbrook Fountain Wellhead, a gift to the City of Oakland in 1914, is the centerpiece of the Mediterranean garden. \nDecomposed granite paths radiate out among mounded beds of Mediterranean plants in five different color palette combinations. The garden provides inspiration for gardening with low water-use plants appropriate for the Bay Area. But besides getting ideas for your own water-wise planting, you can just relax on one the teak benches, watch the bees and hummingbirds pollinating the flowers, and allow yourself to be drawn away to thoughts of the beautiful gardens of Europe or other Mediterranean regions of the world. \nThis garden continues to evolve, and delight, however, thanks to a loyal group of volunteers who come the first Saturday morning of every month, weather permitting, to weed, rake, prune, and plant. Won\’t you join us? We have gloves and tools, of just show up and bring your own!</string>
    <string name="waterSportsInfo">Lake Merritt is a unique saltwater tidal lake conveniently located in the center of downtown Oakland, adjacent to Lakeside Park. Boating programs are offered at Lake Merritt and the Oakland Estuary. Youth and Community Programs provide an entry point to gain skills to explore the wonders of Bay Area boating. Join the Green revolution to learn sailing and muscle-powered boating! You can rent pedal boats, rowboats, kayaks, and sailboats at the Sailboat House. If you want to learn more about the lake, you can take a guided, private charter on a pontoon, dragonboat, or whaleboat. </string>
    <string name="fairyLandInfo"> The year 1948 was a prehistoric era for children\'s entertainment. There was no Disneyland or Nickelodeon TV, and most amusement parks catered to thrill-seeking teenagers. The few kiddielands in the U.S. included a simple carousel, pony ride, and cotton-candy stand. A favorite way to think of our park was summed up in San Francisco magazine in 2004. Children\’s Fairyland, they said, it\’s as miniature and uncynical as a toddler\’s beating heart. We agree. Children\’s Fairyland is, in many ways, a timeless reminder of the joys of standing three-feet tall. \nChildren\’s Fairyland continues to hold fast to its founding vision to be a magical fantasy world where young children can create, imagine, play, and learn. We believe that with the support of families, businesses, and community groups who believe in our mission and in the boundless potential of young children, Children\'s Fairyland will enjoy many years of \’happily ever after\’.</string>
    <string name="exerciseInfo"> People of all ages and cultures come to the Lake Merritt to get fit and stay healthy. You will see many jogging, walking, group yoga, fitness boot camps and the famous Cleveland Cascade 250 foot stairway that you can walk, run or just look at. The stairway is not for the faint of heart. </string>
    <string name="fleaMarketInfo"> Oakland Grand Lake Farmers Market is widely acclaimed as the best farmers market in the East Bay. Oakland residents have made a ritual of this farmers market; anxiously awaiting Saturday morning to head over to Splash Pad Park to pick up their fruits and vegetables direct from their farmer and enjoy lunch on the lawn. The Oakland farmers market is open every Saturday, year-round, rain or shine, from 9am to 2pm. The Oakland Grand Lake market features over 40 local farmers, 30 specialty food purveyors, and a handful of local artisans.</string>
    <string name="oaklandMuseumInfo"> Every Friday night 5pm to  9pm, admission is half-price. Age 18 and under  are free.. Join OMCA every Friday for a family-friendly take on a festive night market, with the best in Bay Area curbside cuisine from gourmet food trucks, local beer, wine, and non-alcoholic beverages at the Blue Oak beer garden, live music, and dance lessons. Get creative at family-friendly drop-in workshops, learn from local foodies in the Makers and Tasters Series, and enjoy special guest performers and events.\nWhen the Oakland Museum of California (OMCA) first opened its doors more than forty years ago, it brought together three historically independent disciplines art, history, and natural science under one roof. This progressive multidisciplinary approach was to celebrate the many facets of California. Our collections comprising more than 1.9 million objects including seminal art works, historical artifacts, ethnographic objects, natural specimens, and photographs and our programs explore and reveal the factors that shape California character and identity, from its extraordinary natural landscapes, to successive waves of migration, to its unique culture of creativity and innovation.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_description">Information</string>
    <string name="portal_address">1611 2nd Ave</string>
    <string name="jong_ga_address">372 Grand Ave</string>
    <string name="grand_lake_address">576 Grand Ave</string>
    <string name="rockin_crawfish_address">211 Foothill Blvd</string>
    <string name="haddon_address">504 Wesly Ave</string>
    <string name="arizmendi_address">3265 Lakeshore Ave</string>
    <string name="michel_address">3343 Lakeshore Ave</string>
    <string name="alley_address">3325 Grand Ave</string>
    <string name="offthegrid_address">1000 Oak St</string>
    <string name="thegardens_address">666 Bellevue Ave</string>
    <string name="japanesegarden_address">666 Bellevue Ave</string>
    <string name="palmgarden_address">666 Bellevue Ave</string>
    <string name="mediterran_address">666 Bellevue Ave</string>
    <string name="waterSport_address">568 Bellevue Ave</string>
    <string name="fairyland_address">699 Bellevue Ave</string>
    <string name="exercise_address">Lake Merritt</string>
    <string name="fleaMarket_address"><![CDATA[Grand Ave & Lake Park Ave]]></string>


</resources>
