<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LakeMerrittGuide</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="place_name">Place name</string>
    <string name="listAddress">place location</string>
    <string name="search_hint">search</string>


    <string name="address_info">address here</string>
    <string name="portal_info">Portal, the best restaurant and open-air beer garden in Oakland, is a beer garden with a large out-door patio with breath-taking view of the Lake Merritt. Order some delicious food made from only the best fresh ingredients and pair it with one of our top notch gourmet beers. </string>
    <string name="jongGA_info">Jong Ga serve from traditional Hanjeongsik to All You Can Eat B.B.Q with a varied array of Banchans (side dishes) \nSince 2000 \nWe are an authentic Korean restaurant committed to serving the finest traditional Korean cuisine. Jong Ga House, meaning the eldest son's house or the head family. We have been serving the bay areasince 2000 and have been garnering favorable reviews. We serve Korean barbeques and hanjeongsik, a full-course Korean meal with a varied array of banchan. Our head chef is an expert in the Korean royal court cuisine and has been preparing
        authentic Korean meals for more than 30 years. Our commitment to quality and friendly service will make your dining experience very pleasurable, and we will continue to uphold a high standard of quality in serving fine Korean cuisine.\nHan Oak \nWhen you enter our restaurant, you will be notice with our beautiful Hanok interior. Hanok is a term to describe Korean traditional houses and it has long been built on the soil of the Korean peninsula. A Hanok has a framework involving a stylobate (a stepped platform as the foundation of the structure) at the bottom,
        and the placement of wooden pillars, beams, rafters and titles at the top. The raw materials used in Hanok, such as soil, timber, and rock, are all natural and recyclable and do not cause pollution. This unique traditional house that has been formed through a long period of time possesses practicality and artistic beauty, and we hope that those who visit our restaurant can see the merits of the Korean traditional house.</string>
    <string name="grandLakeKitchen_info">Grand Lake Kitchen is a great breakfast place. The service here is outstanding, friendly and efficient. Grand Lake Kitchen's have a great patio out front with umbrellas and a view of the Lake. </string>
    <string name="rockinCrawfish_info">ROCKIN' CRAWFISH \nWhether you are a transplant to California from New Orleans, the Crawfish capital of the world, or you just crave the sheer unbridled joy of great seafood eating, you will always remember the day that you found one of our Rockin' Crawfish locations in Oakland or Concord or San Pablo in Northern California. \nOur delicious seafood has a uniquely Cajun flavor that we know you will love.
        We also offer a full line of beverages including both Domestic and Imported Beers, Sake, or delicious Sakitinis served with† your choice of fruit from lychees to mango or peach. \nFor starters we offer an appetizer list that is sure to have something you're craving. Choose from Cajun chili cheese fries or Buffalo wings to seafood gumbo or oysters on the half shell, but remember to†save room for your main course!
On our menu you will find great Cajun seafood offerings including crawfish, crab, shrimp, clams and oysters, and for families we've included some kid friendly items as well, like chicken strips with fries. Add your choice of sides, including rice, potatoes or corn, and your dinner is complete. And don't think we've forgotten about desert - you will love our fried Oreos with strawberries and ice cream.
        \nYou only enter Rockin' Crawfish once as a stranger - by the time you leave you will love our food and come back often.</string>
    <string name="haddonHill_info">A Nice cozy atmosphere for drinks. It's tiny, yet adorable neighborhood cafe serving quality coffee drinks and solid snacks. The owner and staff here are incredibly warm and inviting </string>
    <string name="arizmendiBakery_info">At Arizmendi Bakery on Lakeshore, we offer our community artisan breads, morning pastries and gourmet pizza, prepared right in front of you and brought fresh from our ovens daily. Our focus is on providing healthy food using straightforward recipes and quality ingredients. Ask us for a list of our organic ingredients. \nOur ovens are running all day long. Stop by early for hot muffins, scones and pastries, including some vegan treats. For lunch or dinner, we offer a unique vegetarian pizza of the day featuring seasonal vegetables, infused oils, and fresh herbs on organic, thin sourdough crust. And our signature sourdoughs and hearty wheat breads are hot out of the oven mornings and afternoons. You’ll also find a rotating selection of fresh green salads and spreads in our deli case, as well as soups made from scratch. \nArizmendi is the shortened name of Jose Maria Arizmendiarrieta, a young priest who inspired and helped found the Mondragon Cooperatives in the Basque Country of Spain in the 1950s. Although worker cooperatives have functioned in most parts of the world since the 19th century, the success of the Mondragon Cooperatives has attracted worldwide attention. What started as one firm and roughly 25 people in 1956 is now a major international business with a work force of over 100,000, employed in some 250+ worker-owned enterprises and affiliated organizations.</string>
    <string name="michelBistro_info">Bonjour, \nWe are proud to introduce Michel Bistro ñ a new concept of French bistro. We are from Provence in the south of France and are excited to share our love of cuisine and all that it entails with Oakland. Our goal is to bring to Lakeshore avenue a bistro that offers French dishes with a modern twist, made with high quality products in a relaxed setting. Our signature drink is Pastis, a famous aperitif from Marseille. We want our guests to experience our warm Southern French culture that brings people together with good food, drinks, and atmosphere. We are excited to become part of the community and look forward to creating long-lasting relationships with our customers.</string>
    <string name="theAlley_info">The Alley is voted one of Oakland's greatest dive bars. You do not have to be a drinker to enjoy this bar either, as they have a great greasy spoon type menu. \nThe atmosphere is inviting, and the ambience is dark. There are a million business cards on the walls (probably holding them together) and they also line the tables. Some of the cards look like they have been there as long as the building. There is live karaoke on Sunday nights and this was the thing that everyone can experienced.</string>
    <string name="offTheGrid_info">info here</string>

    <string name="theGardenInfo">garden info here</string>
    <string name="japaneseGardenInfo"> info here</string>
    <string name="palmGardenInfo"> info here</string>
    <string name="mediterraneanGardenInfo"> info here</string>
    <string name="waterSportsInfo"> info here</string>
    <string name="fairyLandInfo"> info here</string>
    <string name="exerciseInfo"> info here</string>
    <string name="fleaMarketInfo"> info here</string>
    <string name="oaklandMuseumInfo"> info here</string>
    <string name="title_activity_description">DescriptionActivity</string>

</resources>
